# **MURARO SIMONE**

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

simone.muraro.95@amail.com

+39 3402785583

Padua (PD), Italy

28 years old

m www.linkedin.com/in/simone-muraro

simone-muraro.com





# **ABOUT ME**

My main strength is my logical and analytical way of thinking. I'm a fast learner, adaptable to any situation and willing to put in the effort required to achieve my goals.

After two years of working as an application consultant, I decided to transition to a more technical and stimulating role. I dedicated several months to full-time learning of programming, and ultimately, I secured my current position at Wintech SPA.



# IT SKILLS

## JavaScript/TypeScript

MERN stack, Angular, React, Node, NestJS, Express, APIs, jQuery, EJS

## HTML/CSS

Responsiveness, Bootstrap

## **Python**

Langchain, Flask, web scraping, API, GUI (Tkinter)

#### Java

Java Spring, Spring Boot

#### **Databases**

SQLite, Oracle SQL, MongoDB, ChromaDB

Basic knowledge of Git and GitHub

Academic knowledge of MATLAB and R



# **OTHER SKILLS**

# Languages

# Italian

Native language

## **English**

В2

### German

A2

# Soft skills

- > problem solving
- work organization
- > handling responsibilities
- client relationship



# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Software developer Feb. 2024 - now Engineering

Software developer. I am currently involved in developing a project aimed at integrating Al into business processes, focusing on retrieving information from a document database using natural language.

Company solution consultant May 2021 - Apr. 2023 Engineering

Application specialist at the Hospital in Padua, with a role of responsibility and autonomy in the management of various activities, such as customer training and assistance, database maintenance and much more.



# **EDUCATION**

Online courses Apr. 2023 - Nov. 2023 Udemy

I learnt programming independently. Check out my developer portfolio at <u>simone-muraro.com</u>

Master's degree in Bioengineering Sept. 2018 - Apr. 2021 Università degli Studi di Padova

Final mark: 101/110



## **CERTIFICATIONS**

State Exam for Professional Information Engineer Dec. 2021 Università degli Studi di Padova